(Penny:)So how was work today?
(Leonard:)Well, I spent most of the afternoon
growing isotopically pure crystals...
(Leonard:)...for neutrino detection.
(Penny:)That sounds like fun.
- Yeah, it was.
- Oh, good, I guessed right.
- Who you talking to?
- Oh, just this guy I met at school.
(Leonard:)Oh, great. We're still dating, right?
(Penny:)Relax, he's just a friend. We're doing
an oral report together. He's really nice.
(Leonard:)I'm sorry, what was that?
I had a little stroke after "oral."
(Penny:)Would you stop?
He moved here from London.
He doesn't know anybody.
(Leonard:)Oh, good, an English accent,
the sexiest accent you can have.
(Penny:)No, that's not true.
(Penny:)There's French, there's Italian.
(Penny:)No, you're right, it's the best.
- Did you tell him you have a boyfriend?
- It didn't come up.
(Leonard:)Maybe you should tell him.
(Penny:)What am I supposed to say?